Guide to the HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm, 1907-1993
HERE General Secretary-Treasurer's Files on Microfilm.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Miscellaneous Correspondence.
  - American Express., 1991; 10 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 01716 on Files reel 32.
  - AT&T., 1991; 11 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 01785 on Files reel 32.
  - AT&T. Transmittal Reports., 12 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 01912 on Files reel 32.
  - Auditel., 1991; 13 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 02103 on Files reel 32.
  - Auto Correspondence., 1991; 14 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 02114 on Files reel 32.
  - Auto Leases., 1991; 15 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 02325 on Files reel 32.
  - Bookkeeping. Memoes., 1991; 16 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 02404 on Files reel 32.
  - Canadian Regional., 1991; 17 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 02594 on Files reel 32.
  - CIE., 1991; 18 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 02612 on Files reel 32.
  - Cheek, Marsha., 1991; 19 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 02662 on Files reel 32.
  - Condo-New York, NY., 1991; 20 (Reel 32)
    Beginning at frame 02737 on Files reel 32.
  - Condo-Plaza., 1991; 1 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 33.
  - Courier/Express., 1991; 2 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00094 on Files reel 33.
  - D'Agostino, Joseph., 1991; 3 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00141 on Files reel 33.
  - Dupont Building., 1991; 4 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00194 on Files reel 33.
  - Dupont Building. Rentals. Closed., 1991-1992; 5 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00197 on Files reel 33.
  - Dorman, Mike., 1991; 6 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00239 on Files reel 33.
  - Employer Identification. IRS., 1991; 7 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00255 on Files reel 33.
  - Employee Lunch Program., 1991; 8 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00281 on Files reel 33.
  - Expense Reimbursement Policy., 1991; 9 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00288 on Files reel 33.
  - Fifty-Year Pins., 1991; 10 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00376 on Files reel 33.
  - Filings. State/Local., 1991; 11 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00407 on Files reel 33.
  - Form Letters., 1991; 12 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00428 on Files reel 33.
  - "G" Miscellaneous., 1991; 13 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00453 on Files reel 33.
  - Give Away Items., 1991; 14 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00456 on Files reel 33.
  - Goldberg, David., 1991; 15 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00466 on Files reel 33.
  - Government of the District of Columbia., 1991; 16 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00552 on Files reel 33.
  - Guernsey Office Products., 1991; 17 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00562 on Files reel 33.
  - HERE Computer Program., 1991; 18 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00566 on Files reel 33.
  - H.E.R.E.I.U. Monthly Statements., 1990-1991; 19 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00711 on Files reel 33.
  - H.E.R.E.I.U. Receipts and Disbursements., 1991; 20 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00746 on Files reel 33.
  - H.E.R.E.I.U. Welfare/Pension Funds. General Correspondence., 1991; 21 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00782 on Files reel 33.
  - IBM Corporation., 1991; 22 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00824 on Files reel 33.
  - Insurance International Union., 1991; 23 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00828 on Files reel 33.
  - "J" Miscellaneous., 1991; 24 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00844 on Files reel 33.
  - JAL/NIKKO, 1991; 25 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00852 on Files reel 33.
  - Juliano, Robert., 1991; 26 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00917 on Files reel 33.
  - Kamber Group., 1991; 27 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00933 on Files reel 33.
  - Kelly Press., 1991; 28 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00950 on Files reel 33.
  - LA Health/Welfare., 1991; 29 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 00983 on Files reel 33.
  - Lee, Raymond., 1991; 30 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01130 on Files reel 33.
  - Local Unions. Exhibit 1., 1991; 31 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01212 on Files reel 33.
  - "M" Miscellaneous., 1991; 32 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01333 on Files reel 33.
  - Marquardt Printing. Local Wage Supplements., 1991; 33 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01341 on Files reel 33.
  - Marquardt Printing. Miscellaneous Orders., 1991; 34 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01418 on Files reel 33.
  - Marquardt Printing. Receipt Book Orders., 1991; 35 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01494 on Files reel 33.
  - Members-At-Large., 1991; 36 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01540 on Files reel 33.
  - Memoes., 1991; 37 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01621 on Files reel 33.
  - Monroe Business., 1991; 38 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01696 on Files reel 33.
  - National Rainbow Coalition., 1991; 39 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01711 on Files reel 33.
  - Office Expenses., 1991; 40 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01718 on Files reel 33.
  - OPEIU. Local 98., 41 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01728 on Files reel 33.
  - Organizing. Correspondence., 1991; 42 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01743 on Files reel 33.
  - Orton, Robert., 1991; 43 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01838 on Files reel 33.
  - Palm Springs Regional., 1991; 44 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01885 on Files reel 33.
  - Phoenix Systems., 1991; 45 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01894 on Files reel 33.
  - Perry, David., 1991; 46 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01910 on Files reel 33.
  - Pershing Account., 1991; 47 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01969 on Files reel 33.
  - Research Office. Los Angeles., 1991; 48 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 01980 on Files reel 33.
  - Resume., 1991; 49 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 02012 on Files reel 33.
  - Reynolds, John., 1991; 50 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 02202 on Files reel 33.
  - Rhinelander Regional Office., 1991; 51 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 02266 on Files reel 33.
  - Riggs National Bank. Closed., 1991-1992; 52 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 02311 on Files reel 33.
  - ROLM, 1991; 53 (Reel 33)
    Beginning at frame 02412 on Files reel 33.
  - Ruiz, Daniel., 1991; 1 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 34.
  - Scimeca, Anthony., 1991; 2 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00046 on Files reel 34.
  - Silbert, Roy., 1991; 3 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00055 on Files reel 34.
  - State Labor Councils., 1991; 4 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00073 on Files reel 34.
  - Stephenson, Arlene., 1991; 5 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00081 on Files reel 34.
  - TIP Education Fund., 1991; 6 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00188 on Files reel 34.
  - Union Labor Life Insurance., 1991; 7 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00205 on Files reel 34.
  - United Health Care. Closed.., 1991; 8 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00221 on Files reel 34.
  - Union Friendly., 1991; 9 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00263 on Files reel 34.
  - Vision Service Plan., 1991; 10 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00358 on Files reel 34.
  - Valverde, Lydia., 1991; 11 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00444 on Files reel 34.
  - "W" Miscellaneous., 1991; 12 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00507 on Files reel 34.
  - Western Regional Office., 1991; 13 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00520 on Files reel 34.
  - Wilhelm. CA & NV Locals., 1991; 14 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00668 on Files reel 34.
  - Winner, Wagner & Associates., 1991; 15 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00863 on Files reel 34.
  - Workmans Compensation., 1991; 16 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00929 on Files reel 34.
  - Xerox., 1991; 17 (Reel 34)
    Beginning at frame 00932 on Files reel 34.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Miscellaneous Files. Ero Records Through 1984.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1 (Reel 35)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 35.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1985; 2 (Reel 35)
    Beginning at frame 00006 on Files reel 35.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1984; 3 (Reel 35)
    Beginning at frame 00048 on Files reel 35.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1983; 4 (Reel 35)
    Beginning at frame 00380 on Files reel 35.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1982; 5 (Reel 35)
    Beginning at frame 00739 on Files reel 35.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1981; 6 (Reel 35)
    Beginning at frame 01100 on Files reel 35.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1980; 7 (Reel 35)
    Beginning at frame 01480 on Files reel 35.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1979; 8 (Reel 35)
    Beginning at frame 01974 on Files reel 35.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1978; 1 (Reel 36)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 36.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1977; 2 (Reel 36)
    Beginning at frame 00558 on Files reel 36.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1976; 3 (Reel 36)
    Beginning at frame 01224 on Files reel 36.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1975; 4 (Reel 36)
    Beginning at frame 01650 on Files reel 36.
  - International Union. Correspondence., 1973-1974; 5 (Reel 36)
    Beginning at frame 01778 on Files reel 36.
  - Gladstone, Fred., 1975; 6 (Reel 36)
    Beginning at frame 01923 on Files reel 36.
  - Grogan, Barney., 1980-1981; 7 (Reel 36)
    Beginning at frame 02446 on Files reel 36.
  - Fragomeni, Frank L., Jr., 1978; 8 (Reel 36)
    Beginning at frame 02470 on Files reel 36.
  - Eastern Regional Office. Herman Leavitt Files., 1981-1982; 1 (Reel 37)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 37.
  - Eastern Regional Office. Herman Leavitt Files. (continued)., 1981-1982; 1 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 00006 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank, Washington, DC. General., 1973-1985; 2 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 00822 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank. Checking Account Deposits., 3 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 00903 on Files reel 38.
  - H.E.R.E.I.U. Deposits., 1985; 4 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 00904 on Files reel 38.
  - H.E.R.E. Checking Deposits., 1984; 5 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 00911 on Files reel 38.
  - Deposits., 1983; 6 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 00947 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank. Checking Account Deposits from International Union., 7 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 00983 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank. Checking Account Deposits from International Union., 8 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 01026 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank. Checking Account Deposits., 9 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 01218 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank. Savings Account Deposits., 10 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 01356 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank. Savings Account Deposits., 11 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 01357 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank. Savings Account Withdrawal., 12 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 01421 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank. Savings Account Withdrawal., 13 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 01422 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank. Checking Account Statements., 14 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 01426 on Files reel 38.
  - Riggs National Bank. Checking Account Statements., 15 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 01427 on Files reel 38.
  - Internal Revenue Service., 16 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 02040 on Files reel 38.
  - Internal Revenue Service., 1984-1985; 17 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 02041 on Files reel 38.
  - Internal Revenue Service., 1984; 18 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 02208 on Files reel 38.
  - Internal Revenue Service., 1983; 19 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 02278 on Files reel 38.
  - Internal Revenue Service., 1982; 20 (Reel 38)
    Beginning at frame 02433 on Files reel 38.
  - Internal Revenue Service., 1981; 1 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00005 on Files reel 39.
  - Internal Revenue Service., 1978-1980; 2 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00122 on Files reel 39.
  - Internal Revenue Service., 1974-1977; 3 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00279 on Files reel 39.
  - Internal Revenue Service. Taxes. W-4s, 4 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00508 on Files reel 39.
  - Personal Property Taxes., 5 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00523 on Files reel 39.
  - Personal Property Taxes., 6 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00524 on Files reel 39.
  - Accounting Ledgers., 1974-1982; 7 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00745 on Files reel 39.
  - Accounting Ledgers., 1974-1975; 8 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00746 on Files reel 39.
  - Accounting Ledgers., 1976-1977; 9 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00795 on Files reel 39.
  - Accounting Ledgers., 1981-1982; 10 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00835 on Files reel 39.
  - Accounting Ledgers., 1977-1979; 11 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00859 on Files reel 39.
  - Accounting Ledgers., 1979-1981; 12 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00884 on Files reel 39.
  - Ledgers., 13 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00920 on Files reel 39.
  - General Ledger., 1974-1975; 14 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00921 on Files reel 39.
  - General Ledger., 1975-1976; 15 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00942 on Files reel 39.
  - General Ledger., 1976-1978; 16 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00963 on Files reel 39.
  - General Ledger., 1978-1979; 17 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00982 on Files reel 39.
  - Receipt and Disbursement Ledgers., 1973-1978; 18 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 00998 on Files reel 39.
  - Disbursements., 1978-1980; 19 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01166 on Files reel 39.
  - Disbursements., 1981-1982; 20 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01283 on Files reel 39.
  - Ledger Books., 1983-1985; 21 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01373 on Files reel 39.
  - Audits., 22 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01510 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1984; 23 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01511 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1983; 24 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01563 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1982; 25 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01625 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1981; 26 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01711 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1980; 27 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01798 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1979; 28 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01892 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1978; 29 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 01982 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1977; 30 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 02053 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1976; 31 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 02101 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1975; 32 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 02174 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1974; 33 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 02262 on Files reel 39.
  - Quarterly Audit Reports., 1973; 34 (Reel 39)
    Beginning at frame 02351 on Files reel 39.
- Series General Secretary-Treasurer. Local Correspondence. 1981-1982.
  - Local 1., 1982; 1 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00003 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 2., 1981; 2 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00081 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 2., 1982; 3 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00124 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 2. Shortage., 1980; 4 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00155 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 3., 1981; 5 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00187 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 3., 1982; 6 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00217 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 5., 1981; 7 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00247 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 5., 1982; 8 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00289 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 6., 1981; 9 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00334 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 6. Loan., 1981; 10 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00455 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 6., 1982; 11 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00463 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 8., 1981; 12 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00568 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 8., 1982; 13 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00648 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 9., 1979; 14 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00722 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 56., 1981; 78 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02141 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 56., 1982; 79 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02153 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 56. Loan., 1982; 80 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02184 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 57., 1981; 81 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02213 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 57., 1982; 82 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02221 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 62., 1981; 83 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02229 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 62. Loan., 1981; 84 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02241 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 62., 1982; 85 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02263 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 64., 1981; 86 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02267 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 64., 1982; 87 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02278 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 65., 1981; 88 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02287 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 65., 1982; 89 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02294 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 66., 1981; 90 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02300 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 66., 1982; 91 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02303 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 69., 1981; 92 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02320 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 69., 1982; 93 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02341 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 73., 1981; 94 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02358 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 73., 1982; 95 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02374 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 74., 1981; 96 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02377 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 74., 1982; 97 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02396 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 75., 1981; 98 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02416 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 75., 1982; 99 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02467 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 76., 1981; 100 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02485 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 76., 1982; 101 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02486 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 83., 1981; 102 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02502 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 83., 1982; 103 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02503 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 86., 1981; 104 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02513 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 86., 1982; 105 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02605 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 99., 1981; 106 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02661 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 99., 1982; 107 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02667 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 99. Loan., 108 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02674 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 101., 1981; 109 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02727 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 101., 1982; 110 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02733 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 103., 1981; 111 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02745 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 103., 1982; 112 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02746 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 104., 1981; 113 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02750 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 104., 1982; 114 (Reel 40)
  - Local 104. Loan., 1982; 115 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02752 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 116., 1981; 116 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02818 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 116., 1982; 117 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02826 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 118., 1981; 118 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02832 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 118., 1982; 119 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02853 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 122., 1981; 120 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02861 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 122., 1982; 121 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02866 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 126., 1981; 122 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02884 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 126., 1982; 123 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02885 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 134., 1981; 124 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02895 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 134., 1982; 125 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02899 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 135., 1981; 126 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02914 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 135., 1982; 127 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02924 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 136., 1981; 128 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02925 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 136., 1982; 129 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02926 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 144., 1981; 130 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02929 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 144., 1982; 131 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02945 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 150., 1981; 132 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02948 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 150., 1982; 133 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02961 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 151., 1981; 134 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02972 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 151., 1982; 135 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02978 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 155., 1981; 136 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02981 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 155., 1982; 137 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 02986 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 163., 1981; 1 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00003 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 163., 1982; 2 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00004 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 165., 1981; 3 (Reel 41)
    Beginning at frame 00007 on Correspondence reel 2.
  - Local 9., 1980; 15 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00733 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 9., 1981; 16 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00742 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 9. Loan., 1981; 17 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00781 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 9., 1982; 18 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00888 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 10., 1981; 19 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00929 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 10., 1982; 20 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00955 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 11., 1981; 21 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 00994 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 11., 1982; 22 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01008 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 12., 1981; 23 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01034 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 12., 1982; 24 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01038 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 14., 1981; 25 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01044 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 14., 1982; 26 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01056 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 15., 1982; 27 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01086 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 16., 1982; 28 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01059 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 17., 1981; 29 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01097 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 17., 1982; 30 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01105 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 18., 1981; 31 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01123 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 18., 1982; 32 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01147 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 19., 1981; 33 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01156 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 19., 1982; 34 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01159 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 21., 1982; 35 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01175 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 23., 1981; 36 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01181 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 23., 1982; 37 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01187 on Correspondence reel 1.
  - Local 24., 1981; 38 (Reel 40)
    Beginning at frame 01215 on Correspondence reel 1.